{
  "players": [],
  "questions": [
    {
      "id": 1,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of known species of insects on Earth?",
      "answer": "1000000"
    },
    {
      "id": 2,
      "question": "How many kilometers does light travel in one year (light-year)?",
      "answer": "9_461_000_000_000"
    },
    {
      "id": 3,
      "question": "What is the current estimate of the age of the universe in years?",
      "answer": "13_800_000_000"
    },
    {
      "id": 4,
      "question": "How many human taste buds does the average person have?",
      "answer": "10_000"
    },
    {
      "id": 5,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of neurons in the human brain?",
      "answer": "86_000_000_000"
    },
    {
      "id": 6,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of cats are there according to the International Cat Association (TICA)?",
      "answer": 73
    },
    {
      "id": 7,
      "question": "What is the current world record for the highest recorded temperature on Earth, in degrees Celsius?",
      "answer": 56.7
    },
    {
      "id": 8,
      "question": "How many moons does the planet Saturn have?",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 9,
      "question": "What is the total number of bones in the adult human body?",
      "answer": 206
    },
    {
      "id": 10,
      "question": "How many countries are members of the United Nations?",
      "answer": 193
    },
    {
      "id": 11,
      "question": "What is the speed of sound in air at sea level, in meters per second?",
      "answer": 343
    },
    {
      "id": 12,
      "question": "How many chromosomes are there in a human cell, excluding sex chromosomes?",
      "answer": 44
    },
    {
      "id": 13,
      "question": "In the periodic table, what is the atomic number of gold (Au)?",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "id": 14,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of known species of mammals on Earth?",
      "answer": 6400
    },
    {
      "id": 15,
      "question": "How many verses are there in William Wordsworths poem, I Wandered Lonely as a Cloud?",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 16,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded number of push-ups in one hour?",
      "answer": 2806
    },
    {
      "id": 17,
      "question": "How many elements are there in the periodic table?",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "id": 18,
      "question": "What is the population of the most populous country in the world?",
      "answer": "1,409,517,397"
    },
    {
      "id": 19,
      "question": "In how many languages is the Universal Declaration of Human Rights available?",
      "answer": 508
    },
    {
      "id": 20,
      "question": "How many squares are there on a standard chessboard?",
      "answer": 204
    },
    {
      "id": 21,
      "question": "What is the record for the longest time (in days) a person has spent in space in a single mission?",
      "answer": 437
    },
    {
      "id": 22,
      "question": "How many national parks are there in the United States?",
      "answer": 63
    },
    {
      "id": 23,
      "question": "How many Oscars did the film Titanic win at the 1998 Academy Awards?",
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 24,
      "question": "How many time zones are there in the world?",
      "answer": 38
    },
    {
      "id": 25,
      "question": "What is the average wingspan (in feet) of an adult albatross?",
      "answer": "11 feet"
    },
    {
      "id": 26,
      "question": "What is the speed of the fastest land animal, the cheetah, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": 75
    },
    {
      "id": 27,
      "question": "How many books are in the Old Testament of the Bible?",
      "answer": 39
    },
    {
      "id": 28,
      "question": "What is the record for the most goals scored by a single player in a FIFA World Cup tournament?",
      "answer": 13
    },
    {
      "id": 29,
      "question": "In how many countries is Spanish the official language?",
      "answer": 21
    },
    {
      "id": 30,
      "question": "What is the speed of light in a vacuum, in meters per second?",
      "answer": "299,792,458"
    },
    {
      "id": 31,
      "question": "How many countries are there in Africa?",
      "answer": 54
    },
    {
      "id": 32,
      "question": "What is the record (in feet) for the longest snake ever recorded?",
      "answer": "33 feet (Python, reticulatus)"
    },
    {
      "id": 33,
      "question": "How many hearts does an octopus have?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 34,
      "question": "What is the boiling point of water in Fahrenheit?",
      "answer": 212
    },
    {
      "id": 35,
      "question": "What is the population of India, as of the latest estimate?",
      "answer": "1,366,000,000"
    },
    {
      "id": 36,
      "question": "In the game of Scrabble, how many tiles are there in the full set?",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "id": 37,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human hand?",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 38,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of players on a standard baseball teams roster?",
      "answer": 40
    },
    {
      "id": 39,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of dogs are there according to the American Kennel Club (AKC)?",
      "answer": 197
    },
    {
      "id": 40,
      "question": "How many chromosomes are there in a potato cell?",
      "answer": 48
    },
    {
      "id": 41,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded temperature on Earth, in degrees Fahrenheit?",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "id": 42,
      "question": "In how many languages is the Bible available?",
      "answer": 3386
    },
    {
      "id": 43,
      "question": "How many strings does a standard violin have?",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 44,
      "question": "What is the total number of squares on a chessboard?",
      "answer": 64
    },
    {
      "id": 45,
      "question": "How many petals does a typical daisy flower have?",
      "answer": 34
    },
    {
      "id": 46,
      "question": "What is the record for the longest recorded flight (in seconds) of a paper airplane?",
      "answer": "27.9 seconds"
    },
    {
      "id": 47,
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a housefly?",
      "answer": "28 days"
    },
    {
      "id": 48,
      "question": "How many episodes are there in the original Star Trek television series?",
      "answer": 79
    },
    {
      "id": 49,
      "question": "In how many countries is the sport of cricket popular?",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "id": 50,
      "question": "How many valves does a trumpet typically have?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 51,
      "question": "What is the total number of squares on a standard Sudoku grid?",
      "answer": 81
    },
    {
      "id": 52,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is recreational marijuana use legal?",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 53,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest time (in minutes) a person has held their breath underwater?",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 54,
      "question": "How many keys are there on a standard piano?",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "id": 55,
      "question": "How many legs does a lobster have?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 56,
      "question": "What is the record for the most points scored in a single NBA game?",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "id": 57,
      "question": "How many members are there in the European Union (EU)?",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 58,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of players on a standard ice hockey team?",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 59,
      "question": "How many legs does a caterpillar typically have?",
      "answer": 16
    },
    {
      "id": 60,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human skull?",
      "answer": 22
    },
    {
      "id": 61,
      "question": "In how many dimensions do string theories propose the universe exists?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 62,
      "question": "How many elements are there in the Noble Gases group of the periodic table?",
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "id": 63,
      "question": "What is the record for the most goals scored in a single soccer (football) match?",
      "answer": 149
    },
    {
      "id": 64,
      "question": "How many constellations are officially recognized by the International Astronomical Union?",
      "answer": 88
    },
    {
      "id": 65,
      "question": "What is the record for the longest recorded distance (in kilometers) traveled by a human in space?",
      "answer": "879.4, million kilometers (Scott Kelly)"
    },
    {
      "id": 66,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human vertebral column (spine)?",
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "id": 67,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of players on a standard basketball teams roster?",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 68,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded wind speed on Earth, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": 231
    },
    {
      "id": 69,
      "question": "In how many countries is the sport of rugby played?",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "id": 70,
      "question": "How many players are there on a standard field lacrosse team during a game?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 71,
      "question": "What is the world record for the most consecutive push-ups without a break?",
      "answer": "10,507 (Charles, Servizio)"
    },
    {
      "id": 72,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded altitude (in feet) reached by a human-powered aircraft?",
      "answer": "96,863feet"
    },
    {
      "id": 73,
      "question": "How many phases are there in the moons lunar cycle?",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 74,
      "question": "What is the record for the longest recorded flight of a bird, in miles?",
      "answer": "44,000 miles (Arctic Tern)"
    },
    {
      "id": 75,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded waterfall in the world, in meters?",
      "answer": "979(Angel Falls)"
    },
    {
      "id": 76,
      "question": "How many elements are there in the Earths crust?",
      "answer": 118
    },
    {
      "id": 77,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is the sport of ice hockey played professionally?",
      "answer": 32
    },
    {
      "id": 78,
      "question": "How many countries are part of the European Free Trade Association (EFTA)?",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 79,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded speed of a manned aircraft, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": "4,520 (North American X-15)"
    },
    {
      "id": 80,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human foot?",
      "answer": 26
    },
    {
      "id": 81,
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a red blood cell in the human body, in days?",
      "answer": 120
    },
    {
      "id": 82,
      "question": "In how many countries is the sport of badminton popular?",
      "answer": 165
    },
    {
      "id": 83,
      "question": "What is the record for the longest recorded distance run (in miles) by a human in 24 hours?",
      "answer": "188.59 miles (Yiannis, Kouros)"
    },
    {
      "id": 84,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of players on a standard rugby union team during a match?",
      "answer": 15
    },
    {
      "id": 85,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of horses are there according to the International Encyclopedia of Horse Breeds?",
      "answer": 577
    },
    {
      "id": 86,
      "question": "How many valves does a typical saxophone have?",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "id": 87,
      "question": "What is the average length of the small intestine in an adult human, in feet?",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 88,
      "question": "How many recognized species of penguins are there?",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 89,
      "question": "What is the highest recorded wave ever surfed, in feet?",
      "answer": "101.4 (Garrett McNamara)"
    },
    {
      "id": 90,
      "question": "How many keys are there on a standard computer keyboard?",
      "answer": 104
    },
    {
      "id": 91,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest free-fall parachute jump, in feet?",
      "answer": "135,890 (Alan,Eustace)"
    },
    {
      "id": 92,
      "question": "What is the average weight of an adult human brain, in pounds?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 93,
      "question": "How many medals did the swimmer Michael Phelps win at the 2008 Beijing Olympics?",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 94,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is the sport of golf played professionally?",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 95,
      "question": "What is the record for the most points scored in a single NFL season by a team?",
      "answer": "606, Denver Broncos 2013)"
    },
    {
      "id": 96,
      "question": "What is the average length of the adult human esophagus, in inches?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 97,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is the sport of tennis played professionally?",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 98,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of players on a standard American football teams roster?",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "id": 99,
      "question": "What is the world record for the most consecutive backflips on a pogo stick?",
      "answer": "177 (Dalton Smith)"
    },
    {
      "id": 100,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human forearm?",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 101,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is the sport of mixed martial arts (MMA) regulated?",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 102,
      "question": "How many recognized species of dolphins are there?",
      "answer": 90
    },
    {
      "id": 103,
      "question": "In how many U.S. states is the sport of golf played professionally?",
      "answer": 50
    },
    {
      "id": 104,
      "question": "How many keys are there on a standard accordion?",
      "answer": 41
    },
    {
      "id": 105,
      "question": "What is the world record for the deepest free-dive without fins, in meters?",
      "answer": 129
    },
    {
      "id": 106,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human hand and wrist?",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 107,
      "question": "What is the average height of the Great Wall of China, in meters?",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 108,
      "question": "In how many minutes does the average person fall asleep?",
      "answer": 7
    },
    {
      "id": 109,
      "question": "What is the record for the highest number of push-ups in one hour?",
      "answer": 2682
    },
    {
      "id": 110,
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a mayfly, in hours?",
      "answer": 24
    },
    {
      "id": 111,
      "question": "In how many days does the Moon complete one orbit around the Earth?",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 112,
      "question": "How many chromosomes does a human sperm or egg cell contain?",
      "answer": 23
    },
    {
      "id": 113,
      "question": "What is the average temperature of the human body in degrees Celsius?",
      "answer": 37
    },
    {
      "id": 114,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest recorded hiccuping episode, in years?",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "id": 115,
      "question": "What is the average length of a giraffes neck, in feet?",
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "id": 116,
      "question": "How many vertebrae are there in the adult human spine?",
      "answer": 33
    },
    {
      "id": 117,
      "question": "In how many seconds does light travel from the Sun to the Earth?",
      "answer": 500
    },
    {
      "id": 118,
      "question": "What is the average length of an adult blue whale, in feet?",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 119,
      "question": "How many petals does a typical daffodil flower have?",
      "answer": 6
    },
    {
      "id": 120,
      "question": "In how many years does Halleys Comet complete one orbit around the Sun?",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "id": 121,
      "question": "How many planets are visible to the naked eye from Earth?",
      "answer": 5
    },
    {
      "id": 122,
      "question": "What is the world record for the most hot dogs eaten in 10 minutes?",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "id": 123,
      "question": "In how many seconds does the Earth rotate once on its axis?",
      "answer": 86400
    },
    {
      "id": 124,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest ski jump ever performed, in meters?",
      "answer": 253.5
    },
    {
      "id": 125,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest recorded flight of a bird, in days?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 126,
      "question": "What is the average speed of a sneeze, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": 100
    },
    {
      "id": 127,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest wave surfed, in feet?",
      "answer": 101.4
    },
    {
      "id": 128,
      "question": "What is the average weight of an adult male African elephant, in tons?",
      "answer": 12
    },
    {
      "id": 129,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest recorded time without sleep, in days?",
      "answer": 11
    },
    {
      "id": 130,
      "question": "In how many days does it take Venus to complete one orbit around the Sun?",
      "answer": 225
    },
    {
      "id": 131,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of elephants are there?",
      "answer": 3
    },
    {
      "id": 132,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest recorded jump by a horse, in feet?",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 133,
      "question": "In how many countries is the sport of rugby played?",
      "answer": 121
    },
    {
      "id": 134,
      "question": "How many bones are there in the adult human hand?",
      "answer": 27
    },
    {
      "id": 135,
      "question": "What is the average length of an adult blue whale, in feet?",
      "answer": 82
    },
    {
      "id": 136,
      "question": "In how many days does it take Pluto to complete one orbit around the Sun?",
      "answer": 90553
    },
    {
      "id": 137,
      "question": "What is the average speed of the fastest bird, the peregrine falcon, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": 240
    },
    {
      "id": 138,
      "question": "What is the average weight of an adult male gorilla, in pounds?",
      "answer": 400
    },
    {
      "id": 139,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of seahorses are there?",
      "answer": 47
    },
    {
      "id": 140,
      "question": "What is the average length of an adult human femur, in inches?",
      "answer": 19
    },
    {
      "id": 141,
      "question": "In how many years does it take Jupiter to complete one orbit around the Sun?",
      "answer": 11.86
    },
    {
      "id": 142,
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a mosquito, in days?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 143,
      "question": "In how many minutes does it take light to travel from the Sun to the Earth?",
      "answer": 8.3
    },
    {
      "id": 144,
      "question": "What is the average weight of an adult male lion, in pounds?",
      "answer": 420
    },
    {
      "id": 145,
      "question": "What is the average height of Mount Everest, in feet?",
      "answer": 29032
    },
    {
      "id": 146,
      "question": "What is the average lifespan of a red panda, in years?",
      "answer": 8
    },
    {
      "id": 147,
      "question": "What is the average speed of the fastest shark, the shortfin mako, in miles per hour?",
      "answer": 60
    },
    {
      "id": 148,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest jump by a human, in feet?",
      "answer": 8.8
    },
    {
      "id": 149,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest ski jump ever performed, in meters?",
      "answer": 253.5
    },
    {
      "id": 150,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of chickens are there according to the American Poultry Association?",
      "answer": 53
    },
    {
      "id": 151,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest recorded flight of a bird, in days?",
      "answer": 10
    },
    {
      "id": 152,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of spiders are venomous to humans?",
      "answer": 30
    },
    {
      "id": 153,
      "question": "What is the world record for the most hot dogs eaten in 10 minutes?",
      "answer": 76
    },
    {
      "id": 154,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest recorded temperature on Earth, in degrees Fahrenheit?",
      "answer": 134
    },
    {
      "id": 155,
      "question": "What is the world record for the longest recorded hiccuping episode, in years?",
      "answer": 68
    },
    {
      "id": 156,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of rabbits are there according to the American Rabbit Breeders Association?",
      "answer": 49
    },
    {
      "id": 157,
      "question": "What is the world record for the fastest time to solve a 3x3 Rubiks Cube blindfolded, in seconds?",
      "answer": 17.65
    },
    {
      "id": 158,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of ducks are there according to the Domestic Waterfowl Club?",
      "answer": 123
    },
    {
      "id": 159,
      "question": "How many recognized breeds of turtles are there?",
      "answer": 327
    },
    {
      "id": 160,
      "question": "What is the world record for the highest ski jump ever performed, in meters?",
      "answer": 253.5
    },
    {
      "id": 161,
      "question": "What is the sum of the squares of the first 10 positive integers?",
      "answer": 385
    },
    {
      "id": 162,
      "question": "How many lines are there in a sonnet?",
      "answer": 14
    },
    {
      "id": 163,
      "question": "What is the value of the mathematical constant gamma (γ), correct to three decimal places?",
      "answer": 0.577
    },
    {
      "id": 164,
      "question": "How many movements are there in Wolfgang Amadeus Mozarts Symphony No. 40?",
      "answer": 4
    },
    {
      "id": 165,
      "question": "What is the value of the mathematical constant pi^2, correct to three decimal places?",
      "answer": 9.87
    },
    {
      "id": 166,
      "question": "What is the distance from the Earth to the Moon in kilometers?",
      "answer": 384400
    },
    {
      "id": 167,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of stars in the Milky Way galaxy?",
      "answer": "100,000,000,000"
    },
    {
      "id": 168,
      "question": "What is the average distance between Earth and the Sun in kilometers?",
      "answer": "149,600,000"
    },
    {
      "id": 169,
      "question": "How many different amino acids are there?",
      "answer": 20
    },
    {
      "id": 170,
      "question": "What is the maximum number of electrons in the third energy level of an atom?",
      "answer": 18
    },
    {
      "id": 171,
      "question": "What is the approximate mass of the Great Pyramid of Giza in tons?",
      "answer": "6,500,000"
    },
    {
      "id": 172,
      "question": "What is the gravitational acceleration on the surface of the Moon in meters per second squared?",
      "answer": 1.62
    },
    {
      "id": 173,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of neurons in the human brain?",
      "answer": "86,000,000,000"
    },
    {
      "id": 174,
      "question": "How many protons are there in the nucleus of a uranium-238 atom?",
      "answer": 92
    },
    {
      "id": 175,
      "question": "What is the approximate age of the Earth in billions of years?",
      "answer": 4.54
    },
    {
      "id": 176,
      "question": "What is the approximate number of known exoplanets discovered as of December 2023?",
      "answer": 5100
    },
    {
      "id": 177,
      "question": "How many times does the heart of a hummingbird beat per minute on average?",
      "answer": 1200
    },
    {
      "id": 178,
      "question": "What is the approximate depth of the Mariana Trench in meters?",
      "answer": 11000
    }
  ]
}